cinnamonspiceandeverythingnice.com 2017-08-09

# Privacy Policy | Cinnamon-Spice & Everything Nice

Cinnamon Spice & Everything Nice is committed to maintaining the privacy and protection of your personal information. This privacy policy tells you about the information we collect on our website and how we use that information. By using the Cinnamon Spice & Everything Nice website, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy policy, which may be modified from time to time by us. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

The information we gather falls into two categories: information you supply when you leave comments on the site, and tracking information collected as you navigate through the site.

**Information Collected When Leaving Comments:**

When you leave comments on Cinnamon Spice & Everything Nice, you are required to provide your name, e-mail and you have the option of providing your blog or website URL. This information becomes a permanent part of the website when you provide it with a comment, and your name and blog or website URL can be seen by other visitors to the site, including anonymous visitors. Your e-mail **cannot** be seen and will not be shared or sold to any third parties.

**Information Collected Through Tracking Software:**

We use anonymous information to analyze our site traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

All websites that collect traffic data have the ability to monitor visitor information such as IP addresses, browser type, operating system, location, date/time of visit, and information about which areas of the site are visited. We monitor such information via Google Analytics but do not store it in personal files or link it to individuals.

**Information Collected by Third Party Advertisers:**

Cinnamon Spice & Everything Nice carries advertising provided by third party advertising companies including sheknows, Sovrn, Gourmet Ads, Media.net and content.ad when you visit the website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Our advertisers may serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. In addition to cookies, sheknows, Sovrn, Gourmet Ads, Media.net and content.ad may use web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

Cinnamon Spice & Everything Nice has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

You should be aware that any personal information you submit on Cinnamon Spice & Everything Nice in the comments may be read, collected, or used by other users of this Site, including anonymous visitors.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Cinnamon Spice & Everything Nice (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Cinnamon Spice & Everything Nice or the users of this site, or (3) act under circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of this site.

**Third Party Websites:**

Cinnamon Spice & Everything Nice may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

**Contacting  Cinnamon Spice & Everything Nice in regard to this Policy:**

If you have any questions about this policy and our practices related to this site, please feel free to contact us through our contact form located on the top right of the website.

**Changes to This Policy:**

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this privacy policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on Cinnamon Spice & Everything Nice and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the site. It is your responsibility to review this privacy policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.

_This policy was last updated on September 4, 2016._
